Guide to the Duke Family papers on the Duke Farms residence, 1859-2004 and undated RL.01437
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Administrative Records, 1859-2004 and undated
  - Parke-Bernet Price Lists, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Radio-Telephone Calls, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Ad for Security Officer Position at Duke Farms, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Daily Reports, 1980 Jan (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Daily Reports, 1980 Feb (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Daily Reports, 1980 Mar (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Daily Reports, 1980 Apr (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Daily Reports, 1980 May (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Daily Reports, 1980 Jun (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Daily Reports, 1980 Jul (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Daily Reports, 1980 Aug (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Daily Reports, 1980 Sep (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Daily Reports, 1980 Oct (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Daily Reports, 1980 Nov (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Daily Reports, 1980 Dec (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Davis Farm House, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Dog reports, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Guard Schedule, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Halpern Fire, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Invoice for repair to an English admiralty map screen, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Memoranda and invoice for alterations done to House 49 A & B at Duke Farms, 1980-1982 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Memoranda from/to Joseph Goodavage regarding the use of a Psionic box as a means of plant control at Duke Farms, 1980-1982 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Memoranda related to crop production at Duke Farms, 1980-198?? (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Parke-Bernet Price Lists, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Residence roster, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Time and location check sheets, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Automobile mileage, 1981 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Dairy Farm Sanitation Report. Also included are planting schedules as well as corn and hay inventories, 1981 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Daily Reports, 1981 Jan (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Daily Reports, 1981 Feb (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Daily Reports, 1981 Mar (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Daily Reports, 1981 Apr (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Daily Reports, 1981 May (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Daily Reports, 1981 Jun (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Daily Reports, 1981 Jul (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Daily Reports, 1981 Aug (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Daily Reports, 1981 Sep (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Daily Reports, 1981 Oct (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Daily Reports, 1981 Nov (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Daily Reports, 1981 Dec (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Dog reports, 1981 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Estimates for repairs to a Chinese religious statue, 1981 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Guard Schedule, 1981 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Harlem list, 1981 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Invoices for the repair of a Culligan water softener, 1981-1982 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Light outage reports, 1981 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Parke-Bernet Price Lists, 1981 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Residence roster, 1981 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Memoranda and correspondence related to various business activities at Duke Farms, 1981-1994 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda regarding security procedures at Duke Farms. Includes memoranda on the installation of alarms and break-ins at Duke Farms. Also includes a security agreement with Bel Air Patrol to have them guard Falcon Lair, 1981-1984 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Proposal to replace the propane fired boiler in the Main Residence at Duke Farms, 1981 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Purchase order for a set of two bamboo chairs for Duke Farms, 1981 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Time and location check sheets, 1981 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Vehicle replacement/inspection, 1981 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence and memorandum related to various business activities at Duke Farms, 1982-1996 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Duke Employee Handbook, 1982-1987 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Invoice for the installation of a new Portasoft water softener at the Main Residence. Includes service contract, 1982 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Invoice for the repair of the theatre shades, 1982 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Memoranda regarding routine matters of the switchboard operators at the Gatehouse, such as vacation schedules and visitor logs. Includes some monthly totals for visitors at Duke Farms, 1982-1983 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Parke-Bernet Price Lists, 1982 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Sales brochures for a mozzarella cooker for Duke Farms. Includes some cheese making instructions as well, 1982 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Sales brochure for invisible fences, 1982-1984 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Articles about cow breeding, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Commercial agricultural soil test reports for Duke Farms. Also includes articles on organic farming, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Duke Farms cattle inventory, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Duke Farms organizational chart, 1983-1984 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Job descriptions for employees at Duke Farms, especially for Doris Duke's personal staff, 1983-1997 (1 of 2) (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Job descriptions for employees at Duke Farms, especially for Doris Duke's personal staff, 1983-1997 (2 of 2) (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Literature regarding remedies for infected or poisonesd trees, circa 1983 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Memorandum from Liz McConville, Doris Duke's secretary on computer training courses. Includes notes and printed materials about the IBM Commodore 64, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Parke-Bernet Price Lists, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Payroll Journal Entries, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Parke-Bernet Price Lists, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Estimates and plans for renovations to fountains outside Duke Farms, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Newspaper clippings related to different energy sources, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Housing and Dorm Policies, 1985, 1991, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - National Register of Historic Places Inventory - Nomination form and related material, 1985-1987 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Brochure for the boiler in the Main Residence at Duke Farms, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Cow index summaries, 1986-1994 (1 of 2) (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Cow index summaries, 1986-1994 (2 of 2) (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Crop Plan, 1986 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Farmland Assessment, 1986-1990 (1 of 2) (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Farmland Assessment, 1986-1990 (2 of 2) (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Inventory shots for items at Duke Farms. Includes list of items sent from Duke Farms to Rough Point, 1986 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Invoices for appliances purchased for the kitchen at the Main Residence at Duke Farms. Includes appliances for Shangri La and Rough Point, 1986-1987 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Invoices for maid services rendered by the Pavillion Agency, 1986 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Items needing repair and to be purchased at and for Duke Farms, 1986-1990 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Maintenance and housekeeping instructions for repairs and cleaning work to be performed at the Main Residence and throughout Duke Farms, 1986 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Memoranda received by Scott Uwe regarding maintenance repairs at the Main Residence, 1986 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Memoranda regarding routine business matters at Duke Farms. Includes contact numbers and names for Doris Duke's friends/contacts, 1986-1993 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Receipts for cleaning supplies for the Main Residence, 1986 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Duke Farms Tax Returns, 1987-1993 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Estimate for a new Dairy Barn, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - General ledger reports - Duke Farms, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Memoranda regarding routine household matters such as repairs needing to be made around the house. Includes a veterinary report on Tina, Miss Duke's dog, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Petition for Farmland Preservation, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Pets, DF, Endangered species notes and booklet, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Soil and conservation plan at Duke Farms, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Warranties and manuals for kitchen equipment at Duke Farms, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Balance sheets, Duke Farms, 1988-1990 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Lists of linens for the staff at Duke Farms, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Original Cow Registrations, #727 - #869, 1988-1993 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Price comparisons for water testing and carpet upholstery work. Also includes lease between Doris Duke and Frederick Briggs, Fairholm Farms, Newport, RI, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Quarterly statements, Somerset Trust, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Somerset-Raritan Valley Sewage Authority - Easement Agreement, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Squaring off of Southern Boundary - Duke Farms, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Water Test Results, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Boathouse, 1989-1990 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence with Miss Duke and Chandi Heffner from J. Bruce Langhorne regarding transferring music collection, 1989 Sep (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Deer Control, 1989 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Duke Farm Inventory - Brown Striped Bedroom, Pine Bedroom, 1989 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Duke Farm Inventory - Library, Library Hall, Main Entrance, Mens Cloak Room, Ladies Room, 1989 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Duke Farm Inventory - Oak Room, Dining Room, Dining Room Showcase, 1989 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Duke Farm Inventory - Palm Room, Palm Room Showcase, Bamboo Room, Pine Room, 1989 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Duke Farm Inventory - Pink Bedroom, Green Bedroom, Victorian Bedroom, 1989 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Duke Farm Inventory - Second Floor Hall, 1989 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Duke Farm Inventory - Yellow Room, Crystal Room, 1989 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Herd Records, 1989-1995 (1 of 4) (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Herd Records, 1989-1995 (2 of 4) (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Herd Records, 1989-1995 (3 of 4) (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Herd Records, 1989-1995 (4 of 4) (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Individual Horse Records, 1989 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Inventory of Rooms 1 and 2 in the Main Residence at Duke Farms, circa 1989 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Inventory of Tack Room, 1989 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Maintenance requests made by Doris Duke, 1989 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Receipt and related materials for horse jumps. Includes building layout for Coach Barn, 1989 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Winter farm projects, 1989 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Addresses for NY and NJ companies which serve Duke Farms, circa 1990s (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Codes for different locations at Duke Farms, circa 1990s (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Dairy Awards, 1990-1994 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Financial, account book for Duke Farms, Rough Point, Shangri La, and California linens, 1990-1991 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Housing List and Description, 1990 and undated (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Inventory of linen at Duke Farms, Falcon Lair, Rough Point, and Shangri La, 1990-1991 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Invoice, purchase made by Chandi Heffner at Hermes, 1990 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Organic Pest Control, 1990 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Barn Information Sheets, 1991-1996 (1 of 2) (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Barn Information Sheets, 1991-1996 (2 of 2) (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Cow life histories, #5-#781, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Crop Plans and related materials, 1991-1996 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Heifer Life History - Duke Farms, 1991 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Herd Management Options and Decision Values, 1991-1994 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Linen to be used for Miss Duke and Chandi Heffner at Duke Farms, Rough Point, Shangri La, and Falcon Lair, circa 1991-1993 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Memorandum from Paul Smith to Miss Duke regarding trees available for transplanting on the property an the cost to do such transplanting, 1991 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Total Herd Care Dairy Feeding Program, 1991-1994 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Various correspondence and memoranda related to operations of Duke Farms, 1991-2001 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Camels, 1992, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Daily maintenance chores to be completed at the Main Residence, 1992-1993 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Duke Farms Financial Statements, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Duke Farms Organic Farming, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Farm equipment list, motor vehicles, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Heifer Life History - Duke Farms, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Horses, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Instructions for work needing to be performed at the Main Residence, circa 1992 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Invoices and places to purchase items for Duke Farms, circa 1992 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Invoices and receipts related to the sale of cattle, 1992-1994 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - List of Duke Farms Main Residence bills. Includes bills for Miss Duke's purchases as well as medical visits for her pets, 1992 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Statement of Expenses, 1992-1991 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - The Humane Society of the United States, 1992 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Weekly reports from Duke Farms and Rough Point, 1992 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Cupie Singh's grocery lists for the Main Residence, circa 1993 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Duke Farms Employee Handbook, 1993-1994 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Duke Farms Sewer System, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Items to be purchased for Miss Duke, circa 1993 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Invoices for restorations by Costikyan and linen purchase, 1993-1994 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Memoranda related to daily business activities at Duke Farms, 1993-1994 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Memoranda regarding Duke Farms employee Nelly Korok's vacation and work schedule, 1993-1994 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Original Cow Registrations, #870 -, 1993-1997 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Work repairs to be made at the Main Residence, circa 1993 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Cow life histories, #880-891, 1994-1995 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Fabric samples from the Stark Carpet Corporation for the carpets at Duke Farms, 1994 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Memoranda and correspondence related to various business activities at Duke Farms, 1994-1996 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Memorandum from Marianne Bowles, Duke Farms, to Bernard Lafferty. Includes a map of Hillsborough Township, circa 1994 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Request forms for purchase or work project at Duke Farms, 1994, 1996 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Documentation related to tax boundaries at Duke Farms, 1995 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Herd Data, 1995-1997 (1 of 2) (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Herd Data, 1995-1997 (2 of 2) (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Legal documentation related to lease of farm acreage at Duke Farms, 1995-1996 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Pet Health Insurance - Chubs & Kodie, 1995 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - American Jersey Cattle Club - Cow Registration, 1996 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - General Liability - Allocations, 1996 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Individual Cow Pages and Heifers, 1996-1997 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Duke Farms boundary survey, 1997 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Facsimiles regarding repairs at Duke Farms, 1997 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Property Issues, 1998 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Thank you letters to Duke Gardens from school groups that visited display gardens, 2000-2001 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Photocopies of Duke Farms postcards that are part of Special Collections & University Archives at Rutgers, 2002 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Background, Orchid Hybridization, Phalaenopsis Doris, 2003 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Census Records (copies), J.B. Duke, Mr. & Mrs. T. Holt, W. Duke, Samuel Inman, Wm Inman & Nanaline Holt Inman, Inman Family Tree, 2003 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Inman Genealogy, 2004-2005 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Article about how to remove stains from fabrics, undated (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Articles of Agreement between The Raritan Water Power Company and the Somerville Water Company, undated (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Business contract for shoe and belt repair. Includes fabric sample, undated (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Cleaning instructions to remove dog waste stains from a wool carpet, undated (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Copies of Dr. Few & Dr. Edens (Duke University Presidents) correspondence regarding Doris Duke, from Duke University Archives, undated (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Copies of James B. Duke Papers from Duke University Archives, undated (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence related to Andrew Flying Service Ltd., undated (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Inventory of Doris Dukes' record collection, undated (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Inventory of equipment at Duke Farms, undated (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - List of "Miscellaneous Maps Previously Unlisted" which are part of Doris Duke's estate. Includes maps of Hillsborough, Falcon Lair, SEAAC maps, et al, undated (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Paint colors for rooms in Main Residence, undated (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Various copyrighted images of Doris Duke, undated (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Vehicle Appraisals, undated (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Picture inventory of Doris Duke's clothes, undated (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Picture inventory of Doris Duke's clothes, undated (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Picture inventory of Doris Duke's clothes - Cedar Closet, undated (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Picture inventory of fur vault, undated (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Workshop inventory (includes photographs), undated (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Picture inventory of Doris Duke's clothes, undated (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Somerville Residence Work Shop 1st Floor - Articles brought in for repairs, undated (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Dairy Herd Records, 1971-1982 (1 of 2) (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Dairy Herd Records, 1971-1982 (2 of 2) (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Dairy Herd Records, 1974-1981 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Dairy Herd Records, 1984-1985 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Dairy Herd Records, 1985-1986 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Dairy Herd Records, 1986-1989 (1 of 2) (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Dairy Herd Records, 1986-1989 (2 of 2) (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Dairy Herd Records, 1987-1989 (1 of 2) (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Dairy Herd Records, 1987-1989 (2 of 2) (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - American Jersey Cattle Club - Official Performance Certificates, 1991 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Dairy Herd Records, 1991-1994 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper articles, 1900-1905 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Biographical history of NC, 1905 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper articles, 1906-1910 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper articles, 1911-1912 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - American Homes and Gardens article, 1914 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper articles, 1914-1918 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper articles, 1919-1924 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Newspaper articles, 1925-1929 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Newspaper articles, 1930-1934 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Newspaper articles, 1935-1936 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper articles, 1937-1939 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Ladies Home Journal article, 1939 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Newspaper clippings, Alec Cunningham-Reid. Kept together for/by Miss Duke, 1939-1945 (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Newspaper articles, 1940 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Newspaper articles, 1941-1943 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Newspaper articles, 1944-1945 (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Photocopy of Town & Country article, 1947 (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Newspaper articles, 1946-1949 (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - Magazine article, Life, "The Great Lover," Article about Rudolph Valentino, circa 1950s (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - Newspaper articles, 1950-1957 (Box 54, Folder 20)
  - Materials regarding Louis Bromfield, 1955-1956 (Box 54, Folder 21)
  - General interest clippings, 1954-1990 (Box 54, Folder 22)
  - Newspaper articles, 1958-1961 (Box 54, Folder 23)
  - Magazine articles, 1960s-1980s (Box 54, Folder 24)
  - Newspaper articles, 1960-1963 (Box 54, Folder 25)
  - Magazine articles, 1964 (Box 54, Folder 26)
  - Newspaper articles regarding Duke Gardens, 1974 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper articles, 1964-1966 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper Articles, Duke Gardens, 1964-2002 (1 of 2) (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper Articles, Duke Gardens, 1964-2002 (2 of 2) (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper Articles regarding Doris Duke donation for Park Improvement, 1964 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Photocopies of Vogue article, 1966 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper articles, Tirella accident, 1966-1967 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Alumni Register, Duke University, Article "Duke's Mixture,", 1968 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Newspaper articles, 1967-1969 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Journal articles, 1970 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper articles, 1970-1974 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous newspaper clippings about Doris Duke, 1972-1980 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Newspaper articles, SEEAC, 1972 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Newspaper articles, Animal Medical Center, 1974 (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Newspaper articles, NRF, 1974-1978 (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Newspaper clippings pertaining to Animal Medical Center at Duke Farms, 1974, 1976, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Newspaper articles, 1975-1979 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Press Release, "The Dukes of Durham, 1865-1929," by Robert Durden, 1975 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper articles, Detective Lawsuit, 1976-1977 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper articles, 1980-1986 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Magazine articles, 1987-1990 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper articles regarding Imelda Marcos, 1987-1989 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper articles regarding Imelda Marcos, 1988 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Newspaper Articles, 1990-1992 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Newspaper Articles, 1990-1993 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Newspaper Articles, 1993 Jan-Aug (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper Articles, 1993 Sep-Dec (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Magazine Articles, 1994 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Newspaper Articles, 1994 Jan-Jun (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Newspaper Articles, 1994 Jul-Dec (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Magazine Articles, 1995 (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - Newspaper Articles, 1995 Jan-Mar (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper Articles, 1995 Apr (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper Articles, 1995 May (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper Articles, 1995 Jun (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper Articles, 1995 Jul-Sep (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper Articles, 1995 Oct-Dec (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Ephemera, 1996 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Magazine Articles, 1996 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Newspaper Articles, 1996 Jan-Apr (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Newspaper Articles, 1996 May-Dec (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Magazine Articles, 1997 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - North Carolina Historical Review, Durden article, 1997 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Newspaper Articles, 1997 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Newspaper Articles, 1998 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - North Carolina Historical Review, Durden article, 1999 (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Newspaper Articles, 1999 (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - North Carolina Historical Review, Durden article, 2000 (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Newspaper Articles, 2000 (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - Magazine Articles, 2001 (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - Newspaper Articles, 2001 (Box 57, Folder 20)
  - Magazine Articles, 2002 (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - Magazine Articles, 2003 (Box 57, Folder 22)
  - Newspaper Articles, 2004 Jan-May (Box 57, Folder 23)
  - Newspaper Articles, 2005 (Box 57, Folder 24)
  - Magazine Articles, 2006 (Box 57, Folder 25)
  - Newspaper Articles, 2006 (Box 57, Folder 26)
  - Online Articles, 2007 (Box 57, Folder 27)
  - Newspaper Articles, 2008 (Box 57, Folder 28)
  - Online Articles, 2008 (Box 57, Folder 29)
  - Invoices related to windsocks and other forms of electrical supply. 1987 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Invoices and vouchers relating to repairs at House No. 27. 1987–1989 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Invoices for electrical work performed at Duke Farms. 1988 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Estimate for reupholstery work to be performed at Duke Farms. June 21, 1989 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Invoices and purchase order relating to repairs of Building No. 28. 1989 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Invoices and purchase order requisitions relating to roads and catch basins at Duke Farms. 1989 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Invoices and vouchers for general services performed at Duke Farms. 1989 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Invoices and vouchers relating to general services at the Coach Barn/Stables. 1989 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Invoices for repairs at House No. 52. 1992 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Deeds, Mortgages, and Agreements relating to the formation of J.B. Duke’s Hillsborough, N.J. property. 1859–1937, 1946 (1 of 4) (Box 58, Folder 10)